fxreporter.com 2012-05-09

# Forex Trading News - Forex Trading - Forex Trading Reviews - Forex Brokers - FX Reporter

## Privacy Policy

Our company does not share or divulge personal information about our users to a third partys, without the users’ previous approval.

Information we share with our corporate relations facilitates our offer of enhanced service to our users, enables them to save time and money and eases the users’ benefits from the company’s extra value.

Our company can also use the users’ information for some mailing or marketing purposes. The user can choose to reject this.

We gather information of general use about our Website visitors for statistics and administrative intentions. In some cases, cookies can help our Web servers to gather general information. A cookie is a little text file made of alphanumeric characters. The cookie created on a computer when browser that accepts cookies accesses a website that uses cookies. Cookies are used in order to help the users’ browser to navigate a certain website and use all its features. A cookie is used only to help the users’ browser process a website and it does not gather information from the users’ computer.

We can share personal information of a user with third parties that are not in our corporate relations solely when we have the user’s consent or under the subsequent situations: We give the information to reliable partners that work on our behalf or with our company under privacy agreements. They can use the personal information of a user in order to facilitate our communication with the user about offers from our company or our marketing partners. In no case do these companies receive any autonomous right to share the information given. We answer to subpoenas, court orders, or legal procedure, or to set up or exercise our legal rights or protect against legal complaints; We trust that it is necessary to share information for investigation and prevention reasons or in order to take action concerning illegal actions, alleged fraud, situations that involve possible threats to the physical safety or a person, breach of our company’s terms of use, or as otherwise obliged by law. Our company may show targeted ads founded on personal information.

Our users and their privacy is a matter of great respect to our company.

Warm regards
